It may
seem a little cumbersome to you using
this
app, but bear in
mind there is a method to this madness.
There is a reason I've created this app
the way it is done. And I can share with
you that reason. It's not like I have to
keep it a mystery. The primary reason is
if you're not prepared to to do self
exploration, if you're not prepared to
work for your sadena, then you are also
not ready to be initiated into it, then
you're also not ready to actually do
it.
So even though it may seem like a game,
but please even for a moment don't think
it's a game.
The reason it may look like a game is
because I wanted you to experience the
immersive nature of each world where
you'll be performing that sadena. If you
are performing this, it may seem that oh
I have to find my way around it. But the
reason I've made it that way, the reason
we've configured it that way is because
I'd like you to work a little. I'd like
you to enjoy the journey a little. It
would benefit you from experiencing that
world and doing the things you um ought
to be doing in that so that when you go
and perform the main ritual of each
world, you are
truly in it. You are truly devoted. So
there is no way to hasten the process
that we have created uh in here. So
you're always going to start your
journey from
um Mahali. That's the first Mahavidya.
[Music]